

jagritim2002@gmail.com

jagriti-projects.netlify.app

jagriti-portfolio.netlify.app

8805268727

Pen. Maharashtra

# Front End Developer

## **Profile**

Detailed-Oriented Front-End Developer having more than 2+ internships working experience with HTML5, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, Bootstrap5, Jquery. Highly adept at both Independent and a collaborative projects, with an emphasis on the landing pages and website development.

Jagriti Mishra

## Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- BOOTSTRAP5
- JQUERY
- SAAS
- FLEX / GRID
- JAVASCRIPT
- FIGMA
- GIT / GITHUB
- RESPONSIVE WEBSITE
- REACTJS

## Education

BSC - INFORAMTION TECHNOLOGY

Pillai HOC College of Arts, Science and commerce.

2020 - 2023

# Experience

### WEB DEVELOPMENT & DESIGNING

The Sparks Foundation (Feb 2023 - Mar 2023)

- Develop custom web design solutions
- Completed the task which was assigned during the internship.
- Developed Banking Management Website.

### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERN**

Null Class (Nov 2022 - Dec 2022)

- Develop custom web design solutions
- Completed the website by using MERN Stack Language.
- Developed Stackoverflow Clone Website.

#### WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

Code Clause Company (Oct 2022 - Oct 2022)

- Develop custom web design solutions
- Developed Covid-19 website, Sentimental Analysis project and Quiz Game.